so people want solutions here's solutions you're not going to follow any of them but here's
solutions one nobody should be paying any taxes nobody should be paying a lick of taxes folks
are not going to do that because they're afraid to go to jail they're afraid of whatever
no matter what solution that you think there is it is going to be met with repression and because
everybody's afraid of repression they don't want to actually commit the solutions but i'm gonna
give you some solutions so one nobody should be paying taxes two physicians should be providing
their services for free i know y'all are like what yes positions should be providing their
services for free three nobody should be paying for utilities yeah anything that the government
controls federally locally statewide nope nobody should be paying for their water to work their
electricity and people are going to say but then they'll turn off the electricity then they'll turn
off the water well we better get some candles four nobody should be paying rent or mortgage literally
the only way that things change is if you do drastic change it's newton's third law to a
reaction there's an equal and opposite reaction let me tell you something you know what they want
they want us to turn up that's what they want they want us to turn all the way up so they can do
martial law imagine if we turned all the way down like all until we make money obsolete it will
continuously be used to keep us and our democracy which we've never really had obsolete
if you want drastic change you're gonna have to make drastic change but since but because people
in this country don't really know how to do drastic change they don't really want to see
anything really for real change so i'm gonna say that and now everyone's gonna argue with me about
all the reasons why none of these are solutions i also know for a fact that if we applied any of
these solutions these people will come down on us but i also know that's literally what they're
already doing